<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Regulation on </title>
    <link>https://ch-naseem.com/tags/regulation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Regulation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ch-naseem.com/tags/regulation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s Russian Fines, DDR5 Records, and Windows AI Future</title>
      <link>https://ch-naseem.com/blog/post7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ch-naseem.com/blog/post7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;google-faces-astronomical-fines-in-russia&#34;&gt;Google Faces Astronomical Fines in Russia&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ch-naseem.com/images/blogs/7/1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In what might be the largest fine ever imposed on a company, Russian courts have demanded Google pay an almost incomprehensible sum of 2 undecillion rubles (that&amp;rsquo;s a number with 36 zeros!) for failing to restore blocked Russian media channels on YouTube. To put this in perspective, this amount far exceeds the entire world&amp;rsquo;s GDP, which sits at around $100 trillion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The dispute began in 2020 when YouTube blocked certain Russian channels due to U.S. sanctions, with tensions escalating after February 2022 when more channels were blocked. While Google has essentially withdrawn from Russia, declaring its local subsidiary bankrupt in 2022, the legal battle continues globally, with Russian media attempting to seize Google&amp;rsquo;s assets in various countries including Turkey, Hungary, Spain, and South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Latest on AI and Society</title>
      <link>https://ch-naseem.com/blog/post1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ch-naseem.com/blog/post1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;pope-francis-calls-for-international-ai-treaty&#34;&gt;Pope Francis Calls for International AI Treaty&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ch-naseem.com/images/blogs/1/1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&#xA;Earlier this week, Pope Francis released his annual World Day of Peace message, focused this year on artificial intelligence (AI) and peace. The pope called for the global community to work together to adopt a binding international treaty regulating the development and use of AI.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Francis acknowledged the impressive achievements of AI, but also highlighted the risks, like increased inequality and loss of jobs. He emphasized the need for AI systems to uphold human dignity and rights. The pope warned about the use of AI for surveillance, manipulation, and autonomous weapons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
