<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft on </title>
    <link>https://ch-naseem.com/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ch-naseem.com/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s Russian Fines, DDR5 Records, and Windows AI Future</title>
      <link>https://ch-naseem.com/blog/post7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ch-naseem.com/blog/post7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;google-faces-astronomical-fines-in-russia&#34;&gt;Google Faces Astronomical Fines in Russia&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ch-naseem.com/images/blogs/7/1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In what might be the largest fine ever imposed on a company, Russian courts have demanded Google pay an almost incomprehensible sum of 2 undecillion rubles (that&amp;rsquo;s a number with 36 zeros!) for failing to restore blocked Russian media channels on YouTube. To put this in perspective, this amount far exceeds the entire world&amp;rsquo;s GDP, which sits at around $100 trillion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The dispute began in 2020 when YouTube blocked certain Russian channels due to U.S. sanctions, with tensions escalating after February 2022 when more channels were blocked. While Google has essentially withdrawn from Russia, declaring its local subsidiary bankrupt in 2022, the legal battle continues globally, with Russian media attempting to seize Google&amp;rsquo;s assets in various countries including Turkey, Hungary, Spain, and South Africa.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok&#39;s Ban Challenge, Drake&#39;s AI Takedown, Tesla&#39;s Autopilot Probe and Microsoft&#39;s Coding Nostalgia</title>
      <link>https://ch-naseem.com/blog/post5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ch-naseem.com/blog/post5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;tiktok-owner-has-strong-first-amendment-case-against-us-ban-professors-say&#34;&gt;TikTok Owner Has Strong First Amendment Case Against U.S. Ban, Professors Say&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://ch-naseem.com/images/blogs/5/1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Legal experts believe ByteDance, the Chinese owner of TikTok, has a strong First Amendment argument against the recently passed U.S. law that could force a sale or ban of the popular video sharing app. The law specifically names TikTok and ByteDance, raising concerns that it constitutes an unconstitutional &amp;ldquo;bill of attainder&amp;rdquo; by singling out a specific entity for punishment without trial.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
